A Guide to the Clifford Currie Collection on Colvin Run Mill, 1967-2003 (bulk 1968-1972)
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 3: Slides, 1967-2003
  - CRM - Greater Face Wheel Construction, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2-133)
  - CRM - Layout-Cog Wheel, 1971 May (Box 2, Folder 2-134)
  - CRM - Greater Face Wheel Layout, 1971 May (Box 2, Folder 2-135)
  - CRM - Red Hott - Face Wheel Construction, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2-136)
  - CRM - Face Wheel Construction, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2-137)
  - CRM - Face Wheel Construction & Arms, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2-138)
  - CRM - Face Wheel Layout, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2-139)
  - CRM - Assemble Cog Wheel, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2-140)
  - CRM - Lessor Face Wheel Fellows, 1971 August (Box 2, Folder 3-1)
  - CRM - Face Wheel Construction, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3-2)
  - CRM - Currie-Measure Fellows, 1971 May (Box 2, Folder 3-3)
  - CRM - Lessor Face Wheel Shaft-Cutting for Gudgeons, 1971 April (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - CRM - Lessor Face Wheel Shaft Turning Supports, 1971 April (Box 2, Folder 3-5)
  - CRM - Gudgeon End, 1971 April (Box 2, Folder 3-6)
  - CRM - Turning Lessor Face Wheel Shaft, 1971 April (Box 2, Folder 3-7)
  - CRM - LFW Shaft Turning for Gudgeon, 1971 April (Box 2, Folder 3-8)
  - CRM - Lessor Face Wheel Shaft, 1971 April (Box 2, Folder 3-9)
  - CRM - Lessor Face Wheel Shaft, 1971 April (Box 2, Folder 3-10)
  - CRM - Turn Lessor Face Wheel Shaft, 1971 April (Box 2, Folder 3-11)
  - CRM - Grinding Cherry Spindle, 1972 November (Box 2, Folder 3-12)
  - CRM - Cliff Grinding Spindle, 1972 November (Box 2, Folder 3-13)
  - CRM - Constructing Wallower, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 3-14)
  - CRM - Steel Wallower Rounds-Pointed, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 3-15)
  - CRM - Constructing Wallower, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 3-16)
  - CRM - Wallower Construction, 1971 November (Box 2, Folder 3-17)
  - CRM - Constructing Trundle, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 3-18)
  - CRM - Constructing Husk Frame, 1971 June (Box 2, Folder 3-19)
  - CRM - Spindle Bray, 1971 August (Box 2, Folder 3-20)
  - CRM - Spindle Bray, 1971 August (Box 2, Folder 3-21)
  - CRM - Ready for Waterwheel Shaft, 1971 August (Box 2, Folder 3-22)
  - CRM - Bore Shaft Greater Face Wheel, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3-23)
  - CRM - Mortise Greater Face Wheel, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3-24)
  - CRM - Mortise Shaft Greater Face Wheel, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3-25)
  - CRM - GFW & Wallower Installation, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 3-26)
  - CRM - 3 Shafts, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 3-27)
  - CRM - Boring Shaft, 1971 November (Box 2, Folder 3-28)
  - CRM - Mortise LFW Shaft in Cog Pit, 1971 November (Box 2, Folder 3-29)
  - CRM - Set New Gear, 1971 November (Box 2, Folder 3-30)
  - CRM - Place Gearing, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 3-31)
  - CRM - Mortise Shaft Lessor Face Wheel, 1971 November (Box 2, Folder 3-32)
  - CRM - Package New Cogs, 1971 November (Box 2, Folder 3-33)
  - CRM - New Gearing, 1971 November (Box 2, Folder 3-34)
  - CRM - New Gears, 1971 November (Box 2, Folder 3-35)
  - CRM - Setting Gearing, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 3-36)
  - CRM - Spindle & Trundle, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 3-37)
  - CRM - New Gearing, 1971 November (Box 2, Folder 3-38)
  - CRM - Spindle & Trundle, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 3-39)
  - CRM - New Gears, 1971 November (Box 2, Folder 3-40)
  - CRM - Face Wheel Construction Detail, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3-41)
  - CRM - New Gears, 1971 November (Box 2, Folder 3-42)
  - CRM - New Cogs Installation, 1971 November (Box 2, Folder 3-43)
  - CRM - Spindle & Trundle, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 3-44)
  - CRM - Installing Cogs, 1971 November (Box 2, Folder 3-45)
  - CRM - Installing Cogs, 1971 November (Box 2, Folder 3-46)
  - CRM - Boring, 1971 November (Box 2, Folder 3-47)
  - CRM - New Mill Bin, 1971 November (Box 2, Folder 3-48)
  - CRM - New Chimney, 1969 September (Box 2, Folder 3-49)
  - CRM - Snow Mill, 1970 February (Box 2, Folder 3-50)
  - CRM - Snow Mill, 1970 February (Box 2, Folder 3-51)
  - CRM - Mill Race Head, 1972 January (Box 2, Folder 3-52)
  - CRM - Mill Race Head, 1972 January (Box 2, Folder 3-53)
  - CRM - Mill Race Cattails, 1971 September (Box 2, Folder 3-54)
  - CRM - Mill Race & Ducks, 1971 September (Box 2, Folder 3-55)
  - CRM - Colvin Shade Trees Obstruction, 1971 September (Box 2, Folder 3-56)
  - CRM, 1971 November (Box 2, Folder 3-57)
  - CRM, 1971 November (Box 2, Folder 3-58)
  - Old Mills - Old Mills -J.B. Campbell, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3-59)
  - Leaders - Cliff Currie & Red Hott, 1975 September (Box 2, Folder 3-60)
  - Old Mills, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3-61)
  - Old Mills - Roblins Mill, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3-62)
  - Old Mills - Roblins Mill, 1972 January (Box 2, Folder 3-63)
  - Old Mills - Roblins Mill, 1967 September (Box 2, Folder 3-64)
  - Old Mills, 1967 September (Box 2, Folder 3-65)
  - Roblins Mill, 1967 September (Box 2, Folder 3-66)
  - Roblins Mill, 1967 September (Box 2, Folder 3-67)
  - Roblins Mill, 1967 September (Box 2, Folder 3-68)
  - Roblins Mill, 1967 September (Box 2, Folder 3-69)
  - Roblins Mill, 1967 September (Box 2, Folder 3-70)
  - Roblins Mill, 1967 September (Box 2, Folder 3-71)
  - Roblins Mill, 1967 September (Box 2, Folder 3-72)
  - Roblins Mill, 1967 September (Box 2, Folder 3-73)
  - Roblins Mill, 1967 August (Box 2, Folder 3-74)
  - Roblins Mill, 1967 August (Box 2, Folder 3-75)
  - Roblins Mill, 1967 August (Box 2, Folder 3-76)
  - Old Mill?, 1970 February (Box 2, Folder 3-77)
  - Old Mill - Atlanta, 1969 July (Box 2, Folder 3-78)
  - Old Mill - Near Atlanta, 1969 July (Box 2, Folder 3-79)
  - Old Forebay, 1969 July (Box 2, Folder 3-80)
  - Old Mill Wall, 1970 November (Box 2, Folder 3-81)
  - Old Mill Window, 1970 November (Box 2, Folder 3-82)
  - Slate Roof, 1970 November (Box 2, Folder 3-83)
  - Old Mill - Virginia, 1970 November (Box 2, Folder 3-84)
  - Old Mill, 1970 November (Box 2, Folder 3-85)
  - Old Mill Dam, 1970 November (Box 2, Folder 3-86)
  - Old Mill-Complete, 1970 November (Box 2, Folder 3-87)
  - Old Mill, 1970 November (Box 2, Folder 3-88)
  - Old Mill, 1970 November (Box 2, Folder 3-89)
  - Old Mill, 1970 November (Box 2, Folder 3-90)
  - Kline Mill, 1971 August (Box 2, Folder 3-91)
  - Old Mill, 1971 September (Box 2, Folder 3-92)
  - Old Millstone, 1971 September (Box 2, Folder 3-93)
  - Ancient Document, 1970 December (Box 2, Folder 3-94)
  - Old Document, 1970 December (Box 2, Folder 3-95)
  - Rock Creek Park, 1970 April (Box 2, Folder 3-96)
  - Rock Creek Park, 1970 April (Box 2, Folder 3-97)
  - Rock Creek Park, 1970 April (Box 2, Folder 3-98)
  - Rock Creek Park, 1970 April (Box 2, Folder 3-99)
  - Rock Creek Park, 1970 April (Box 2, Folder 3-100)
  - Rock Creek Park, 1970 April (Box 2, Folder 3-101)
  - Mill Pond - Atlanta, 1969 July (Box 2, Folder 3-102)
  - Old Mill Elevators, 1969 June (Box 2, Folder 3-103)
  - Old Kline Mill, 1969 June (Box 2, Folder 3-104)
  - Old Kline Mill, 1969 June (Box 2, Folder 3-105)
  - Old Mill-Virginia, 1969 June (Box 2, Folder 3-106)
  - Old Kline Mill, 1969 June (Box 2, Folder 3-107)
  - Old Kline Mill, 1969 June (Box 2, Folder 3-108)
  - Old Mill Hopper, 1969 June (Box 2, Folder 3-109)
  - Old Mill Gearing, 1969 June (Box 2, Folder 3-110)
  - Documents, 1968 May (Box 2, Folder 3-111)
  - Papers, 1968 May (Box 2, Folder 3-112)
  - Pierce - Waterwheel, 1968 May (Box 2, Folder 3-113)
  - Old Mill Door, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3-114)
  - Pierce Mill - Bolting, 1968 May (Box 2, Folder 3-115)
  - Pierce Mill - 2nd Floor, 1968 May (Box 2, Folder 3-116)
  - Old Mill Dam, 1968 May (Box 2, Folder 3-117)
  - Pierce Mill - Waterwheel, 1968 May (Box 2, Folder 3-118)
  - Pierce Mill - Waterwheel, 1968 May (Box 2, Folder 3-119)
  - Pierce Mill - Waterwheel, 1968 May (Box 2, Folder 3-120)
  - Old Pierce Mill, 1968 May (Box 2, Folder 3-121)
  - Old Pierce Mill - Forebay - Waterwheel, 1968 May (Box 2, Folder 3-122)
  - Old Pierce Mill - Head Race, 1968 May (Box 2, Folder 3-123)
  - Old Mill - Documents, 1968 May (Box 2, Folder 3-124)
  - Old Mill - Documents, 1968 May (Box 2, Folder 3-125)
  - Old Mill, 1968 May (Box 2, Folder 3-126)
  - Old Mill - Documents, 1968 May (Box 2, Folder 3-127)
  - Old Mill - Documents - Pierce, 1968 May (Box 2, Folder 3-128)
  - Old Pierce Mill - Waterwheel, 1968 May (Box 2, Folder 3-129)
  - Pierce, 1970 June (Box 2, Folder 3-130)
  - Pierce, 1970 June (Box 2, Folder 3-131)
  - Pierce, 1970 June (Box 2, Folder 3-132)
  - Pierce - Flood - Rock Creek Park, 1970 June (Box 2, Folder 3-133)
  - Pierce - Flood - Rock Creek Park, 1970 June (Box 2, Folder 3-134)
  - Pierce - Flood - Rock Creek Park, 1970 June (Box 2, Folder 3-135)
  - Pierce - Flood - Rock Creek Park, 1970 June (Box 2, Folder 3-136)
  - Pierce - Flood - Rock Creek Park, 1970 June (Box 2, Folder 3-137)
  - Pierce - Flood - Rock Creek Park, 1970 June (Box 2, Folder 3-138)
  - Pierce - Flood - Rock Creek Park, 1970 June (Box 2, Folder 3-139)
  - Pierce - Flood - Rock Creek Park, 1970 June (Box 2, Folder 3-140)
  - Pierce Mill 2nd Floor, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3-141)
  - 3-Pierce Mill Old Waterwheel, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3-142)
  - Book. “Catalogue of 35mm Slides of Clifford Currie, 1968-1972” Prepared by Bob Lundegard & Nick Yannarell, January 2003, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 4)